https://www.csah.cam.ac.uk/privacy-and-cookie-policies

Council of the School of the Arts and Humanities
Graduate Education CommitteeGraduate Education Committee overview
VacanciesVacancies overview
Recruitment Processes and Selection CommitteesRecruitment Processes and Selection Committees overview
CSAH Academic Appointments Procedure Final.pdf
Approved Selection Committees 2019Approved Selection Committees 2019 overview
Introduction
This page explains what personal information we gather when you visit this web site.
Who will process my personal information?
The information published here applies to the use of your personal information (also known as 'personal data') by the University of Cambridge through the viewing or use of this site.
General personal information collected on our websites
When you visit any of the websites within the Cambridge domain we hold certain information about you for service and security reasons. For more information on this, please seehttps://www.cam.ac.uk/about-this-site/privacy-policy
Further information
For more information about how we handle your personal information, and your rights under data protection legislation, please seehttps://www.information-compliance.admin.cam.ac.uk/data-protection/general-data
Cookies
Users who visit a Falcon site may receive some or all of the Google Analytics cookies if the site administrator has enabled them (whether or not they authenticate).
Sites may embed third-party material (e.g. YouTube videos) and these may carry their own cookies. You must refer to the site's local cookie policy to determine what cookies are being set and for what purpose.
Sites may include 'ShareThis' social media buttons, which will carry cookies if the user has a 'ShareThis' account enabled.
Users who authenticate will receive cookies from the Raven/Shibboleth authentication system.
Cookie
Returned to
Function
P/S*
__utma
Falcon site
Google Analytics
P
P
_shibsession_...
shib.raven.cam.ac.uk
Authentication
S
Ucam-WLS-Session
shib.raven.cam.ac.uk
Authentication
S
JSESSIONID
__stid
Set by "ShareThis" widget if it is embedded on the site. The ShareThis service can identify a visitor if they have separately signed up with ShareThis for a ShareThis account (and provided their consent). This information may be used to display advertisements on sites that include the ShareThis sharing icon - See 'ShareThis' privacy statement.
Social Media buttons
P
*Final column: S marks a session cookie. P marks a persistent cookie.
Session cookies expire when the user quits the browser (or earlier).
Persistent cookies remain within the browser after it is quit and restarted, until they reach their expiry date.
Raven privacy & cookie policy:
http://raven.cam.ac.uk/privacy.html
Google analytics cookie policy:
http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html
Follow us on Twitter
Tweets by CamArtsHums
Latest News
"Reproduction matters to us all": introducing the latest Horizons magazine20 Nov 2020
A treasure trove of unseen writing by Ted Hughes and Seamus Heaney reveals a vital creative friendship14 Nov 2020
Beyond the pandemic: build a greener future09 Nov 2020
More
Around the School
In Memoriam: Judith Jarvis Thomson 4 October 1929-20 November 202007 Dec 2020
The deadline for applications for 2021 entry onto the MPhil in Philosophy and the PhD in Philosophy is Thursday 3rd December 202030 Nov 2020
Spotlight on...
About research at Cambridge
